Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Audio-Visual, 1972-1988, undated; 10
  - Radio Tapes, 1979-1988; 2
    - “The System” & “Reflections on Energy”, 1979 June 1, 8 (Box 425, Folder 4)
    - “Reflections on Energy, Part II” 7 “Now Is the Time”, 1979 June 15, 22 (Box 425, Folder 5)
    - Fuel for Defense & Social Security Funding, 1979 June 29-July 6 (Box 425, Folder 6)
    - “Trade BillEL” & “The President’s Energy Message”, 1979 July 13, 20 (Box 426, Folder 1)
    - “We Should Look to the Experts” & “The Free Market”, 1979 July 27-August 3 (Box 426, Folder 2)
    - “AugustEL” & “Stop the WasteEL”, 1979 August 10, September 14 (Box 426, Folder 3)
    - “The Tip of the Iceberg” & “The Middle EastEL”, 1979 September 21, 28 (Box 426, Folder 4)
    - “The Paper DollarEL” & “U.S. Generous to a Fault”, 1979 October 5, 12 (Box 426, Folder 5)
    - “Bureaucrats & Firearms” & “What Are You Doing About It, Congressman?”, 1979 October 19, 26 (Box 426, Folder 6)
    - “Here We Go Again!” & “Guess Who Is Paying the Bill?”, 1979 November 2, 9 (Box 427, Folder 1)
    - “IranEL” & “The Ultimate Special Interest”, 1979 November 16, 23 (Box 427, Folder 2)
    - “The Middle EastEL” & “Terrorism”, 1979 November 30, December 7 (Box 427, Folder 3)
    - “The President on Nat’l Defense” & “Reflections on the First Year”, 1979 December 14, 21 (Box 427, Folder 4)
    - The Eighties & “The Draft”, 1980 February 8, 15 (Box 427, Folder 5)
    - “Interest RatesEL” & “The Economy”, 1980 February 22, May 9 (Box 427, Folder 6)
    - “The 1981 Budget” & “Refugees”, 1980 May 16, 23 (Box 428, Folder 1)
    - “Where the RubberEL” & “The Eleventh District of Texas”, 1980 May 30, June 6 (Box 428, Folder 2)
    - “The Legislative Process” & “Summer Travels”, 1980 June 13, 20 (Box 428, Folder 3)
    - “More Waste Revealed” & “Ready for the Task Ahead”, 1980 June 27, 1981 February 6 (Box 428, Folder 4)
    - “On Fiscal Responsibility” & “The Reagan Plan”, 1981 February 13, 20 (Box 428, Folder 5)
    - “Productivity” & “A Session with the President”, 1981 February 27- March 6 (Box 428, Folder 6)
    - “Rebuilding National Defense” & The Reagan Plan’s Danger, 1981 March 13, 20 (Box 429, Folder 1)
    - “Defense Department” & Social Security, 1981 May 8, 15 (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - “The Tax DebateEL” & “The Debate Continues”, 1981 July 17, September 25 (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - “Let’s Spend Defense DollarsEL” & Anwar Sadat, 1981 October 2, 16 (Box 429, Folder 4)
    - “The AWACS Debate”, 1981 October 30 (Box 429, Folder 5)
    - “Interest Rates” & “The Continuing Resolution”, 1982 November 13, 27 (Box 429, Folder 6)
    - “The 97th CongressEL” & “The Real Issues”, 1981 December 18, 1982 February 12 (Box 430, Folder 1)
    - Readiness Subcommittee on Defense Waste & “Here We Go Again!”, 1982 February 26, May 7 (Box 430, Folder 2)
    - “We Need Political CourageEL” & “Now It’s Your TurnEL”, 1982 May 14, June 18 (Box 430, Folder 3)
    - “High Interest RatesEL” & “Reflections on 1982EL”, 1982 July 16, 1983 January 7 (Box 430, Folder 4)
    - “The 98th CongressEL” & “Social SecurityEL”, 1983 February 4, 25 (Box 430, Folder 5)
    - “The Real Issues” & “ELAmerica’s Economic Future?”, 1988 April 22, 29 (Box 430, Folder 6)
    - “Our Banking System Revisited”, 1988 May 27 (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - “The War on DrugsEL” & “Let’s Protect Social SecurityEL”, 1988 June 3, 17 (Box 431, Folder 2)
- Oversize Items and Awards, 1954-1994, undated; 11
  As the final series in the collection, Oversize Items and Awards holds physical objects of honors bestowed upon Leath as well as oversized framed photographs. Items of note include Leath’s 1954 diploma from the University of Texas, photographs of county courthouses from his area, and several “Watchdogs of the Treasury Awards.” Other items include plaques, appreciation, service, and merit awards, and framed delegation photographs from throughout his tenure until shortly after in 1994. This series is in no particular order but organized based upon the size and shape of objects and how they fit into storage containers.
  - National Security Leadership Award, undated (Box 432, Folder 1)
  - National Federation of Independent Business (NFIB) Guardian of Small Business Award, 1983-1985 (Box 433, Folder 1)
  - National Federation of Independent Business (NFIB) Guardian of Small Business Award, 1985-1987 (Box 433, Folder 2)
  - Silver Helmet Congressional Award, 1987 (Box 434, Folder 1)
  - NFIB Guardian of Small Business Award, 1979-1981 (Box 435, Folder 1)
  - NFIB Guardian of Small Business Award, 1989-1991 (Box 435, Folder 2)
  - Navy Resale System Advisory Committee, 1990 December (Box 435, Folder 3)
  - NFIB Insignia on Marble Plaque, undated (Box 435, Folder 4)
  - First Turkish F-16 Medallion (& wooden holder), 1987 July (Box 435, Folder 5)
  - Bill Clinton Presidential Inauguration Medallion (& wooden holder), 1993 January 20 (Box 435, Folder 6)
  - Leath Office Doorplate, undated (Box 435, Folder 7)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary of Javits-Wagner-O’Day Act Commemorative Pen, 1988 (Box 436, Folder 1)
  - Bradley Fighting Vehicles Stand and Pen from FMC Corporation, undated (Box 436, Folder 2)
  - Stinger Handheld Missile Plaque, General Dynamics Corporation, Pomona Division, undated (Box 436, Folder 3)
  - Commemorative Plate from General Chavalit, Royal Thai Armed Forces, 1989 (Box 436, Folder 4)
  - Fairchild Republic T-46A Trainer Jet Recognition Award, undated (Box 436, Folder 5)
  - Associated Contractors and Builders “Champion of the Merit Shop” Award, 1985-1987 (Box 436, Folder 6)
  - Disabled American Veterans (DAV) Auxiliary Service Award, 1979 October 27 (Box 437, Folder 1)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars of the United States Service Award, 1979 October 27 (Box 437, Folder 2)
  - DAV Department of Texas Olin E. “Tiger” Teague Congressional Award, undated (Box 437, Folder 3)
  - San Saba County Property Association Service Award, 1979 August 23 (Box 438, Folder 1)
  - Annual National Convention of AMVETS Silver Helmet Congressional Award, 1987 April 4 (Box 438, Folder 2)
  - Military Exchange Services Award, 1990 November 28 (Box 438, Folder 3)
  - Central Texas-Fort Hood Chapter of Association of the United States Army (AUSA) Special Award, 1979 February 23 (Box 439, Folder 1)
  - Sound Dollar Award, 1988 (Box 439, Folder 2)
  - Sound Dollar Award, 1989 (Box 439, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Hispanic Congress Honorary Member, 1987 (Box 440, Folder 1)
  - The American Legion Certificate of Appreciation, 1979-1981 (Box 440, Folder 2)
  - DAV Auxiliary Service Award, 1982 July (Box 440, Folder 3)
  - DAV Service Award, undated (Box 440, Folder 4)
  - Veterans Club of TSTI Award, 1981 March 27 (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Knights of Columbus Law Enforcement Appreciation Night Guest of Honor, 1981 April 21 (Box 441, Folder 2)
  - AUSA Central-Texas Fort Hood Chapter, undated (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Dick and Jane Gephardt, Dick Gephardt for President, Thank-You Plaque, 1990 April 30 (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Chamber of Commerce Spirit of Enterprise Award, 1988-1989 (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - The American Legion Eleventh District Convention, 1979 April 22 (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Andrews Air Force Base (AFB)/ Dan Daniels Golf Tournament, 1994 June 27 (Box 443, Folder 1)
  - Andrews AFB/ Dan Daniels Golf Tournament, 1992 (Box 443, Folder 2)
  - Andrews AFB/ Dan Daniels Golf Tournament, 1993 June 21 (Box 443, Folder 3)
  - Texas National Research Laboratory Commission, Superconducting Super Collider, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 1)
  - Exchange & Commissary News, Leath Leaves Congress, 1989 December 15 (Box 444, Folder 2)
  - National District Attorney’s Association Law Enforcement Appreciation Award, 1985 May 7 (Box 444, Folder 3)
  - American Legion Department of Texas Distinguished Service Award, 1987 (Box 445, Folder 1)
  - Brownwood Chamber of Commerce Service Award, 1983 March 30 (Box 445, Folder 2)
  - DAV Distinguished Service Award, 1985 October 1 (Box 445, Folder 3)
  - Washington Chapter of the National Security Industrial Association Public Service Award, 1990 May 2 (Box 446, Folder 1)
  - National Grocers Association Commemorative Certificate of Merit, 1990 June 21 (Box 446, Folder 2)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action Distinguished Service Award, 1980 June 17 (Box 446, Folder 3)
  - The American Legion Citation of Appreciation, undated (Box 447, Folder 1)
  - United States Chamber of Commerce “It’s Your Business” Panel, 1987 July 15 (Box 447, Folder 2)
  - United States Army Operational Test Command Pin and Patch, 1989 May 26 (Box 447, Folder 3)
  - Leath and Sam Hall in a Conference with President Reagan at the White House, 1982 (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - The National Taxpayer’s Union Taxpayer’s Best Friend Award, 1981 May 4 (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Fort Hood Officers’ Wives Club Honorary Member Certificate, 1981 August 29 (Box 448, Folder 3)
  - National Security Leadership Award, American Security Council Foundation, 1987 (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - National Maritime Day Commemorative Plate, Working Committee of the National Maritime Caucus, 1989 May 22 (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - United States Congressional Advisory Board, American Security Council Foundation, Coalition for Peace Through Strength Leadership Award, undated (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Leath Plaque, Brownwood Mafia, undated (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - American Security Council, Coalition for Peace Through Strength, Leadership Award, undated (Box 450, Folder 2)
  - Leath’s University of Texas Diploma, 1954 May 29 (Box 451, Folder 1)
  - The United States Capitol Historical Society, 1979 January 15 (Box 451, Folder 2)
  - Central Freight Lines 10th of a Century Club Honorary Member, undated (Box 451, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Affairs Committee Framed Black and White Photograph, 97th Congress, 1981-1983 (Box 452, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Affairs Committee Framed Color Photograph, 97th Congress, 1981-1983 (Box 452, Folder 2)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars of the United States Waco Post Service Award, undated (Box 453, Folder 1)
  - American Security Council, Coalition for Peace Through Strength, Leadership Award, 1983 August 3 (Box 453, Folder 2)
  - National Association of Federally Impacted Schools Service Award, 1990 March 6 (Box 453, Folder 3)
  - Honorary Member, Marlin Rotary International, undated (Box 454, Folder 1)
  - Guest Conductor, Amoco/WGMS, undated (Box 454, Folder 2)
  - United State Military Sports Association, undated (Box 454, Folder 3)
  - Groundbreaking Photograph, Waco Metropolitan Area Regional Sewerage System, 1983 May 27 (Box 455, Folder 1)
  - AUSA Award for Distinguished Service, 1984 October 8 (Box 455, Folder 2)
  - “View of the [Demilitarized Zone] DMZ from the Camp Greaves PX” Framed Photograph, undated (Box 455, Folder 3)
  - Leath and Brock Adams (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 456, Folder 1)
  - United State Navy Band Country Current (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 456, Folder 2)
  - Marlin Mills, Inc. Plant (Framed Photograph) signed by company president Roy Jennings, undated (Box 456, Folder 3)
  - City of Brownwood Proclamation of Congressman Marvin Leath Day, 1983 March 29 (Box 457, Folder 1)
  - Falls County, Texas, Flag Plaque, 1984 November 11 (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - American Security Council, Coalition For Peace Through Strength Leadership Award, undated (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Drawing of West Front, Monticello, Home of Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 458, Folder 1)
  - Brownwood Mafia Resolution, 1980 (Box 458, Folder 2)
  - Texas Veterans Affairs Resolution, 1982 December 9 (Box 458, Folder 3)
  - Ceremonial Shovel, Groundbreaking Ceremonies, Universal Services Fort Hood, Inc. Housing Project, 1987 July 1 (Box 459, Folder 1)
  - Sketch of Monticello, Al Repple, 1968 (Box 459, Folder 2)
  - Somervell County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 460, Folder 1)
  - Hood County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 460, Folder 2)
  - Bosque County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 460, Folder 3)
  - Mills County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 461, Folder 1)
  - Brown County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 461, Folder 2)
  - Burnet County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 461, Folder 3)
  - Coryell County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Falls County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 462, Folder 2)
  - Coleman County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 462, Folder 3)
  - San Saba County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 463, Folder 1)
  - McCulloch County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 463, Folder 2)
  - Comanche County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 463, Folder 3)
  - Erath County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 464, Folder 1)
  - Hamilton County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 464, Folder 2)
  - Williamson County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 464, Folder 3)
  - Bell County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Milam County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 465, Folder 2)
  - Lampasas County Courthouse (Framed Photograph), undated (Box 465, Folder 3)
  - Leath 1983-1984 Congressional Calendar (Box 466, Folder 1)
  - Texas Democratic Delegation (Photograph) (1 of 2), 1984 June 20 (Box 466, Folder 2)
  - Texas Democratic Delegation (Photograph) (2 of 2), 1984 June 20 (Box 466, Folder 3)
  - Texas Democratic Delegation (Color Photograph) (1 of 2), undated (Box 466, Folder 4)
  - Texas Democratic Delegation (Black and White Photograph) (2 of 2), undated (Box 466, Folder 5)
  - Ninety-Sixth Congress, U.S. House of Representatives, 1979 (Box 466, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Photograph (Box 466, Folder 7)
  - Distinguished Guest, 28th Annual Conference, National Guard Association of Texas, undated (Box 467, Folder 1)
  - National Associated Businessmen Watchdog of the Treasury Award, 1979-1980 (Box 467, Folder 2)
  - Watchdogs of the Treasury, Inc. Award, 98th Congress, 2nd Session, 1984 (Box 467, Folder 3)
  - Watchdogs of the Treasury, Inc. Award, 100th Congress, 2nd Session, 1988 (Box 467, Folder 4)
  - Watchdogs of the Treasury Award, 101st Congress, 1st Session, 1989 (Box 467, Folder 5)
  - World War II Bombsight, United Technologies Norden Systems, 1987 April 27 (Box 467, Folder 6)